stembook.org 2019-05-03

# Terms and Conditions | StemBook

**IOS PRESS STEMBOOK WEBSITE**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

[http://stembook.org](https://content.iospress.com/page/privacy) is the website platform of _StemBook_ , owned by IOS Press, registered at Nieuwe Hemweg 6B, 1013 BG Amsterdam, The Netherlands.

Guarding your privacy is very important to us. In this Privacy Policy, you can learn which data IOS Press collects via this site and how it is used. It is our goal to provide you with a useful, hassle-free experience while using this website, which requires a certain amount of data collection. If you do not agree with the policies set forth in this Privacy Policy, we recommend that you do not visit the IOS Press _StemBook_ website. 

If you are simply browsing our site without signing in or being recognized by IP address, we will only keep anonymized log data about usage of our site (see 'Cookies' below).

**Which details are collected?**  
\- Contact details that you have provided to us, including demographics  
\- Information on usage of (parts) of our website, including number of downloads  
\- Information about transactions made  
\- Information on alerts that you have installed  
\- Any other information that you have provided to us in order to be able to help you use our website to meet your needs as well as possible 

How IOS Press uses the data collected  
We may use the data collected through our site to:  
\- Establish and verify the identity of our users  
\- Personalize the site for you  
\- Enable you to access and use our site  
\- Fine-tune our services provided to you  
\- Handle financial transactions smoothly and accurately  
\- Collect payments from you  
\- Improve our products and services offered on the IOS Press _StemBook_ website

In the event that we share the data gathered with agents working on our behalf, these agents must assure us that they use the data in a discrete manner. They may not distribute the collected data further and are required to comply with our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions. 

Your data will never be sold to third parties.

**Cookies**  
We may place cookies and or other tracking devices in the user’s browser files. Cookies are used to track user behavior. Based on the collected data, we can improve our products and services. 

Cookies can be rejected. If this is done, portions of the IOS Press _StemBook_ website may not be properly usable. 

**Secure Use of the IOS Press StemBook Website**  
In cooperation with Dropsolid, the hosting partner and webmaster of this website, we will do everything in our power to guard your personal details and usage behavior data. Collected data will be stored on secure servers and once you’re recognized by IP or logged in through Username and Password, you will be in a safe, encrypted area so no one can take advantage of the details you have entered. 

**Links to Other Website**  
Through this website you may be redirected or find links to other websites which are not under the control of IOS Press. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites, nor are we responsible for their Privacy Policy. We encourage you to be aware of the privacy policies of other parties to which we link in case they collect any personal data from you.

**Emails**  
We will only send emails to registered users of the _StemBook_ website who opted in at registration to at registration to be kept informed about _StemBook_ or who signed up to receive news (link: <http://tiny.cc/StemBook-signup>). Users can manage their preferences at any time.

**Advertisements**  
Third-party advertising may appear on our website. Usage metrics may be shared with the advertisers, but personal data will never be disclosed. 

**Changes**  
IOS Press reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time as we see fit. If this occurs, we will include an announcement on the _StemBook_ website to notify users of the changes.

IOS Press  
Nieuwe Hemweg 6B  
1013BG Amsterdam  
Tel.: +31 20 688 33 55  
Fax: +31 20 687 00 39  
Email: [info@iospress.nl](mailto:info@iospress.nl)

Version: September 2018
